Ah Sajeev Sir, talking about earnings, the
results of ICC LBR and SDB Financial have come.
Prima facie, we are liking the results of both the companies.
Sir, tell me
what you noticed and what
should be the strategy?
Ah look at the numbers of HDB SDB Financial the
results were good.  Ah, if we
look at profits, they were up 17%.  Ah EM was a
little flat means soft growth was seen.  It
increased by 11% and only that increased but the
NIMS which were good also increased by 8.23%
quarter on quarter and the credit
cost also fell quarter on
quarter so these are their metrics.
What did he say next?
He said that their
book growth will increase by 6 to 7% over and
above nominal GDP.  So you can imagine that
if the nominal GDP is 11% then their
book will grow by 17-18%.  So he has
given this guidance for FI 27.  So that
is a good and important thing and the second
guidance that they have given is that their net
interest margin of NIMS will
remain above 8% in F27.  So both these
things are good.  The numbers have been good.   There does
n't seem to be that much stress.  What
he had said earlier was that there is stress in the CV and USL
portfolio.  He is
saying now that the stress has reduced now.
So that's a good one too.  Is good.  Ah, it remains to be
seen whether it will be able to grow or
not.  But overall the numbers of HDFC HDB
financials were quite good.
Yes, if we talk about ICICI LBR, their GWP was
around Rs
8000 crore and their growth was 70% by bio
wire.  His combine ratio was
also good.  1010 was 1.4%
which is 130 basis points higher.  Ah,
we saw that their claim ratio
improved.  Claim ratio
increased by 80 basis points to 80%.  The commission ratio
fell by 40 basis points.  Ah, their loss ratio was
also low in motor, health,
crop and if we look at PAT,
PAT was a little low, there was 7.3% growth
in YQ4.  The reason for this is that there was lower
capital gains in this quarter and the little
impact that they got was due to health and
that also happened because of a little bit of
claims there,
as I said, the claim ratio had
increased by 130 basis points.  So
he also got to see its impact.  But the overall
number is growth, health and motor
motor lead.  After the GST cut, there is a
lot of demand for them in health
and also motor, motor rules and motor insurance
rules have also changed.  So they are also
seeing good demand there.  So if
we look from the point of view of general insurance, the
numbers of ICICI LBR ah ah top
line were good.  The bottom line was
slightly lower than expected but the rest of the
ratios were good.